<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<st_store>
		<key>
			<label>key</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>11</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The key field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The key field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The key field is too long.  This field must be no more than 11 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</key>
		<store_purchased>
			<label>store_purchased</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>100</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The store_purchased field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The store_purchased field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The store_purchased field is too long.  This field must be no more than 100 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</store_purchased>
		<date_purchased>
			<label>date_purchased</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The date_purchased field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The date_purchased field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</date_purchased>
		<purchased_by>
			<label>purchased_by</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>100</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The purchased_by field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The purchased_by field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The purchased_by field is too long.  This field must be no more than 100 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</purchased_by>
		<price>
			<label>price</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>10</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The price field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The price field is too long.  This field must be no more than 10 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</price>
		<unit_price>
			<label>unit_price</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>10</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The unit_price field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The unit_price field is too long.  This field must be no more than 10 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</unit_price>
		<warranty_price>
			<label>warranty_price</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>10</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The warranty_price field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The warranty_price field is too long.  This field must be no more than 10 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</warranty_price>
		<coupon_amt>
			<label>coupon_amt</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>10</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The coupon_amt field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The coupon_amt field is too long.  This field must be no more than 10 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</coupon_amt>
		<gift_card>
			<label>gift_card</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>10</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The gift_card field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The gift_card field is too long.  This field must be no more than 10 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</gift_card>
		<is_gift>
			<label>is_gift</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>1</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The is_gift field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The is_gift field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The is_gift field is too long.  This field must be no more than 1 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</is_gift>
		<has_receipt>
			<label>has_receipt</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>1</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The has_receipt field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The has_receipt field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The has_receipt field is too long.  This field must be no more than 1 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</has_receipt>
		<date_warranty>
			<label>date_warranty</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The date_warranty field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</date_warranty>
		<warranty_info>
			<label>warranty_info</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>65537</maxlength>
			<invalidType>The warranty_info field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The warranty_info field is too long.  This field must be no more than 65537 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</warranty_info>
		<date_created>
			<label>date_created</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The date_created field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The date_created field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</date_created>
		<date_updated>
			<label>date_updated</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>0</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The date_updated field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The date_updated field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a date value.</invalidType>
		</date_updated>
		<module>
			<label>module</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>3</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The module field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The module field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The module field is too long.  This field must be no more than 3 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</module>
		<parent_key>
			<label>parent_key</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>11</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The parent_key field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The parent_key field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a numeric value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The parent_key field is too long.  This field must be no more than 11 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</parent_key>
		<parent_module>
			<label>parent_module</label>
			<comment/>
			<maxlength>3</maxlength>
			<notProvided>The parent_module field is required but was not provided.</notProvided>
			<invalidType>The parent_module field does not contain valid data.  This field must be a string value.</invalidType>
			<invalidLength>The parent_module field is too long.  This field must be no more than 3 bytes long.</invalidLength>
		</parent_module>
	</st_store>
